// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
     {
    numb: 1,
    question: "6b - 3 = -21; whats b?",
    answer: "-3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "-8",
      "-3",
      "-5"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " 2 + 2y = -2 ; what's y?", 
    answer: "-2",
    options: [
      "-2",
      "-6",
      "-1",
      "4 "
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 6 + 7x = -15 ; What's x?",
    answer: "-3",
    options: [
      "-6",
      "-3",
      "3",
      "-5"
    ]
  },
    

      {
    numb: 4,
    question: " -18 - 5m = 7 ; what's m?",
    answer: "-5",
    options: [
      "7",
      "-5",
      "3",
      "-8"
    ]
  },

     {
    numb: 5,
    question: "-44 - 8n = 4 ; What’s n?",
    answer: "-6",
    options:[
      "3",
      "5",
      "-6",
      "4"
    ]
  },

    {
 numb: 6,
    question: " -22 = 9n + 5 ; What’s n?",
    answer: "-3",
    options: [
      "5",
      "-5",
      "-3",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    
      {
    numb: 7,
    question: " 5 = -25 - 5b ; What’s b? ",
    answer: "-6",
    options: [
      "-8",
      "5",
      "3",
      "-6"
    ]
  },


    
     {
    numb: 8,
    question: " 12a + 3 = - 21 ; What’s a? ",
    answer: "-2",
    options: [
      "-2",
      "3",
      "-5",
      "4"
    ]
  },

    
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: " -25 = 4c + 3 ; What’s c? ",
    answer: "-7",
    options: [
      "7",
      "4",
      "-7",
      "6"
    ]
  },

    
      {
    numb: 10,
    question: " -10 = 7m + 4 ; What’s m? ",
    answer: "-2",
    options: [
      "-2",
      "4",
      "3",
      "-3"
    ]
  },


    
     {
    numb: 11,
    question: " 3 = -13 -4z ; What’s z? ",
    answer: "-4",
    options: [
      "-4",
      "3",
      "69",
      "-42"
    ]
 },

    
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: " 7w + 5 = - 16 ; What’s w? ",
    answer: "-3",
    options: [
      "-5",
      "31",
      "4",
      "-3"
    ]
  },
    

    
     {
    numb: 13,
    question: " 4y + 6 = -10 ; What’s y? ",
    answer: "-4",
    options: [
      "-4",
      "5",
      "–3",
      "11"
    ]
  },

    
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: " 20 = -44 - 8d ; What’s d? ",
    answer: "-8",
    options: [
      "8",
      "-8",
      "6",
      "-3"
    ]
  },

    
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: " 16a - 3 = -35 ; What’s a? ",
    answer: "-2",
    options: [
      "-2",
      "3",
      "-6",
      "-7"
    ]
  },


    
   {
    numb: 16,
    question: " 10 - 3m = 19 ; What’s m? ",
    answer: "-3",
    options: [
      "-3",
      "-4",
      "6",
      "9"
    ]
  },

  
   {
    numb: 17,
    question: " 11d + 3 = -217 ; What’s d? ",
    answer: "-20",
    options: [
      "41",
      "-37",
      "-20",
      "26"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 18,
    question: " 2b + 2 = -8 ; What’s b? ",
    answer: "-5",
    options: [
      "9",
      "4",
      "-5",
      "-8"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 19,
    question: " 13 + 31n = -204 ; What’s n? ",
    answer: "-7",
    options: [
      "-7",
      "4",
      "-9",
      "3"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 20,
    question: " 15w - 3 = -123 ; What’s w?",
    answer: "-8",
    options: [
      "3",
      "-8",
      "13",
      "16"
    ]
  },

];